bornagainamerican.org 2010-06-12

# Born Again American • About Us

Privacy

Declare Yourself is committed to protecting the privacy and security of both new and frequent visitors as well as our supporters and subscribers. Here is our online privacy policy for information collected through our website and through email lists. 

Declare Yourself expects it may need to revise its privacy policy as it develops the features of its future site. Declare Yourself will make reasonable efforts to inform users of any changes, but the spirit of this policy will be maintained, and our policy to never sell, exchange, rent, trade, or give email lists to third parties will never be altered. 

Use of Declare Yourself’s website is not restricted to registered users, and we expect to provide a robust experience to all users. We’ve created some personalization features that we hope will be useful to you and will provide you the most timely and salient information. 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please fell free to email us at:  [info@declareyourself.com](mailto:info@declareyourself.com) This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it 

You can also reach us via US Mail at:  
Declare Yourself  
100 N Crescent Dr Suite 200  
Beverly Hills CA 90210 

**What Declare Yourself will do with your information:**

Declare Yourself will not ever sell or share the personal information you provide or we collect through our website. We will not disclose your information to any entity without your permission. 

**If you sign up for one of our mailing lists:**

Declare Yourself is committed to providing timely updates to our users by email. We will request information from you to enhance our ability to customize our communications with you so you get the information you want. We will collect relevant contact information and enable you to self-select the type of information that you’d like to receive. You will be able to unsubscribe or change your subscriptions at any time. 

**If you submit information:**

Users who submit information will be informed if information is being collected to customize an individual experience or to learn more about visitors in general to improve our site. 

**Cookies:**

If you express an interest in having your information and preferences remembered, you will be able to check a box that allows a permanent cookie to be placed in the browser directory of your computer's hard drive. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website can store on a computer and later use to recognize a user. A cookie cannot be read by any website other than the one that set it up. The purpose of the permanent cookie is to enhance your ability to receive the information you want. 

Declare Yourself may use session cookies to enhance the experience of users who have not registered or accepted a permanent cookie. A session cookie expires when a user closes the browser in which Declare Yourself’s website was viewed. As with all cookies, users can personalize their browser settings to reject session cookies. 

If at some time after you accepted the permanent cookie, you change your mind, you will be able to delete it by altering your profile. 

**IP Addresses and Log File Data:**

IP addresses are ID numbers for the location of your computer or network on the internet. Log files are recordings of the traffic to and from a server. Declare Yourself’s servers log IP addresses for systems administration and  
troubleshooting. We track page hits in the aggregate to track the  
popularity of pages that people visit. With that information we can improve the quality of the site. Declare Yourself does not use these files to collect personally identifying information, and log files and IP addresses are neither stored with nor used in conjunction with personal information. 

**Children's privacy:**

Declare Yourself is concerned about the safety and privacy of children online. Because of this, we will make all efforts to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulations establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not and will not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. Our site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13, and we will develop our site with the capacity to block acceptance of information from children under 13 whenever age-related information is requested. 

It is possible that by fraud or deception by others we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately obtain parental consent or else delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of information by children under 13, please do so by e-mailing us at  \n [info@declareyourself.com.](mailto:info@declareyourself.com.) This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it 

**Security:**

Only select Declare Yourself staff and contracted individuals have access to personally identifiable information provided by visitors to our site. We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving sensitive personal and financial data from our site. These security measures will protect against loss or misuse of your information. In addition, we have taken appropriate security measures in our server environment to protect against the loss or misuse of information that you’ve provided to our site. 

**Please Note:**

The Declare Yourself plans to regularly update and add new features to our website. Because of this, Declare Yourself expects to revise its privacy policy as its site develops. Such amendments will be posted in the privacy policy section of the site. As stated above, the spirit of this policy will be maintained, and our policy to never sell, exchange, rent, trade, or give email lists to third parties will never be altered. Declare Yourself links to other like-minded websites, but is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those websites.
